const quiz = [
{
	id: 1,
	question: "What are the only two countries that DO NOT sell Coca-cola?",
	answers: ["Argentina and Brazil", "Holland and Cuba", "Cuba and North Korea", "Russia and Iran"],
	correct: "Cuba and North Korea"
},
{
	id: 2,
	question: "The entire human populatin can fit into which city?",
	answers: ["Los Angeles", "New York City", "Paris", "Tokyo"],
	correct: "Los Angeles"
},
{
	id: 3,
	question: "Which is the most visited country?",
	answers: ["United States", "Italy", "France", "China"],
	correct: "France"
},
{
	id: 4,
	question: "How many countries DO NOT use the metric system?",
	answers: ["2", "8", "3", "1"],
	correct: "3"
},
{
	id: 5,
	question: "What is the youngest country?",
	answers: ["Moraco", "United States", "South Sudan", "Taiwan"],
	correct: "South Sudan"
},
{
	id: 6,
	question: "What is the most spoken language on earth?",
	answers: ["English", "French", "Spanish", "Mandarin"],
	correct: "Mandarin"
},
{
	id: 7,
	question: "Which city is the most 'bike friendly'?",
	answers: ["New York City", "Toronto", "London", "Copenhagen"],
	correct: "Copenhagen"
},
{
	id: 8,
	question: "Facebook has more users that the total population of which 3 countries?",
	answers: ["U.S., China, and Brazil", "Puerto Rico, Cuba, and Mexico", "Argentina, Brazil, and Venezuela", "South Africa, Congo, and Uruguay"],
	correct: "U.S., China, and Brazil",
},
{
	id: 9,
	question: "Which country has more pets per household?",
	answers: ["Austrailia", "Greece", "Turkey", "New Zealand"],
	correct: "New Zealand",
},
{
	id: 10,
	question: "Which is the World's largest city?",
	answers: ["Moscow", "Rome", "Los Angeles", "Tokyo"],
	correct: "Tokyo",
}
]